<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>InPlay Doc</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on InPlay Doc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>InPlay Inc</copyright><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/testing/rtt-viewer-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/testing/rtt-viewer-guide.html</guid><description>RTT Viewer Guide # Introduction # J-Link RTT Viewer is a Windows GUI application that uses RTT functionality on the debugging host. RTT Viewer can be used independently, opening its own connection to the J-Link and connecting in parallel to the target of the ongoing debugging session or alternatively to it using an existing J-Link connection.
Configuration # Install J-Link # Should install in-dev\tools\ InPlayToolsSetup.exe first, get more information in JFlash Programming Guide</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/solutions/find-my/find-my-sdk-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/find-my/find-my-sdk-guide.html</guid><description>InPlay Find My SDK Guide # Overview # The IN610 Find My SDK is compliant with the most recent versions of both Apple’s Find My Network Accessory Specification and Google’s Find My Device Network Accessory Specification. This guide provides detailed instructions for configuring, compiling, and installing the IN610 Find My SDK to implement an IN610-based Find My Network Accessory. A typical hardware block diagram for a Find My accessory is as below:</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/solutions/modbus/wireless-modbus-demo-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/modbus/wireless-modbus-demo-guide.html</guid><description>Wireless Modbus Demo Guide # Demo Connections # This guide demonstrates connecting the Wireless Modbus Module, featuring a port with four pins: Vin, GND, A, and B.
Likewise, the Sensor and Relay devices offer one or more similar ports, each with pins designated as A, B, GND, and VCC. The &amp;lsquo;A&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;B&amp;rsquo; pins facilitate RS485 connections, while VCC and GND pins cater to power connections, requiring a power supply voltage of 5V or greater.</description></item><item><title/><link>/docs/solutions/modbus/wireless-modbus-module.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/modbus/wireless-modbus-module.html</guid><description>Introduction to the Wireless Modbus Module # Overview of the Modbus Protocol # Modbus is an application-layer messaging protocol, designed in 1979 by Modicon, which facilitates master/slave interaction between devices. A de facto communication standard in industrial electronics, it has the following features:
Master-Slave Architecture: One master device issues commands to one or more slave devices that respond in kind. Data Representation: Modbus categorizes data as either coils (binary) or registers (numeric), offering diverse data manipulation capabilities.</description></item><item><title>Debug Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/testing/debug-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/testing/debug-guide.html</guid><description>Debug Guide # Introduction # Arm Keil MDK (Microcontroller Development Kit) provides robust debugging capabilities that are essential for efficient software development targeting Arm Cortex-M based microcontrollers. This document provides instructions on using the debugging features in Keil.
Debug Step: # Enter debugging and run to main funtion # Enter debug mode, run program from flash to main function.
Open project, double click &amp;ldquo;proj_ble_lp.uvmpw&amp;rdquo; in &amp;ldquo;SDK\in-dev\proj\proj_ble_find_my\build\mdk&amp;rdquo;. Click project option button, select &amp;ldquo;J-Link&amp;rdquo; in &amp;ldquo;Debug&amp;rdquo; page.</description></item><item><title>GATT Programming Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xx/protocol-reference/ble/gatt-programming-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/protocol-reference/ble/gatt-programming-guide.html</guid><description>GATT Programming Guide # Overview # The GATT (Generic Attribute) is a standard profile in BLE protocol which defines a framework of services and characteristics using ATT attributes as building blocks. The ATT protocol defineds a flat set of data structure called attributes, while GATT defines a hierarchy so that the attributes are grouped into primary and secondary services and these services can include characteristics. GATT also defines how a device will discover, read, write, notify, and indicate the characteristics based on ATT attribute access method.</description></item><item><title>HCI Command</title><link>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/testing/hci_command.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/testing/hci_command.html</guid><description>HCI Command # Introduction to BLE HCI Commands # BLE HCI commands are standardized instructions exchanged between the host and the Bluetooth controller to manage and configure Bluetooth communication. These commands enable the host to initiate various actions, such as establishing connections, configuring parameters, and managing the overall behavior of the Bluetooth device.
HCI Command Structure # BLE HCI commands follow a specific structure, adhering to a standardized format that includes an HCI type, opcode, and parameters.</description></item><item><title>InPlay Programmer Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/download/in_prog-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/download/in_prog-guide.html</guid><description>InPlay Programmer Guide # Introduction # The InPlay Programmer is a graphical chip configuration and programming tool for the PC that enables developers to configure and download programs to target boards using InPlay chips via UART. Developers should refer to the chip datasheet to thoroughly understand the configuration options based on their specific application requirements.
The main window of the GUI tool, as shown in Figure 1, is organized into five area:</description></item><item><title>Inplay Transparent Data Transmission (TRx) profile User Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xx/protocol-reference/ble/inplay_trx_profile.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/protocol-reference/ble/inplay_trx_profile.html</guid><description>Overview # The component documented here is a software component that utilizes BLE GATT protocol to fulfill transparent data transmission over BLE devices. It is based on Inplay BLE application framework and provides set of simple APIs for the convenience of application development. Please refer to GATT Programming Guide for details.
The component consists of the Server and the Client part. The server is composed of GATT based services. It includes two characteristic values with one representing receiving (Rx) and the other representing sending (TX) and a client characteristic configuration descriptor.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/introduction.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/introduction.html</guid><description>Introduction to MultiConnNet System # The MultiConnNet is Inplay&amp;rsquo;s proprietary Multi-Connection Private Network system. It is a 2.4GHz wireless communication network based on a private SDR (Software Defined Radio) protocol, utilizing a one-to-many star connection topology.
The system is comprised of two primary components: the gateway module and the node module.
Key Features # Star Topology: The system employs a star connection model, with the gateway serving as the central node for bidirectional communication with multiple node modules, facilitating management and data transmission.</description></item><item><title>JFlash Programming</title><link>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/download/jflash-download-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/download/jflash-download-guide.html</guid><description>JFlash Programming Guide # Introduction # This document provides a guide on how to use J-Flash to download bin file to the IN6XX chip.
J-Flash is a part of the J-Link tool series developed by Segger, offers a reliable solution for programming Flash memory on embedded systems.
Prerequisites # J-Link Debugger hardware.Get it on Segger web site. J-Link Software and Documentation Pack installed on your host computer(Version 7.62 or later is recommended).</description></item><item><title>Module Instruction Set</title><link>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/command-set.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/command-set.html</guid><description>MultiConnNet Module Instruction Set # The MultiConnNet is Inplay&amp;rsquo;s proprietary Multi-Connection Private Network system. It is a 2.4GHz wireless communication network based on a private SDR (Software Defined Radio) protocol, utilizing a one-to-many star connection topology.
The system is comprised of two primary components: the Gateway module and the Node module. The module is connected to the HOST via UART interface, and this instruction set defines the data packet format between the module and the HOST.</description></item><item><title>MP Tool Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/download/mp-tool-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/download/mp-tool-guide.html</guid><description>MP Tool Guide # Introduction # The MP Tool is a tool for mass production downloading and testing, capable of downloading the main program and token, as well as testing RF performance. Please refer to this document for details.</description></item><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/installation/quick-start.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xx/getting-started/installation/quick-start.html</guid><description>Quick Start Guide # Introduction # This document provides a guide as following:
Install development tools Use the configuration tool Build &amp;ldquo;proj_ble_find_my&amp;rdquo; demo project Download image to DK Preparation # InPlay DK Board JLink Debugger InPlay SDK Usb cable. Install Tools # Download and install MDK-ARM Keil µVision (Version 5.21 or later is recommended).
Download and install J-Link Software and Documentation Pack(Version 7.62 or later is recommended).
Install InPlayInc.DeviceFamilyPack. Double click the InPlayInc.</description></item><item><title>User Guide</title><link>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/user-guild.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/user-guild.html</guid><description>MultiConnNet User Guide # Proper module configuration is essential before the MultiConnNet network can operate normally. However, it is necessary to understand the essential information beforehand.
Boot Mode: The module can enter Boot mode when GPIO_0_4 is connected to GND during power-up or reset, allowing for firmware flashing, storage resetting, and other operations.
Interactive Interface: By default, UART1 is used as interface between HOST and module, with GPIO_2_1 and GPIO_2_7 as TX and RX function, 921600 baud rate, 8N1.</description></item></channel></rss>