<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tools on InPlay Doc</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/tools.html</link><description>Recent content in Tools on InPlay Doc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>InPlay Inc</copyright><atom:link href="/docs/in6xxe/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>InPlay OTA App Development Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/tools/ota-app-develop-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/tools/ota-app-develop-guide.html</guid><description>OTA App Development Guide # Overview # This document provides a comprehensive guide for implementing OTA (Over-The-Air) upgrades using an Android application. It details the OTA service structure, command protocols, error handling, and firmware file format required to upgrade the device software reliably.
OTA Service # UUID:
OTA Service: f95a48e6-a721-11e9-a2a3-022ae2dbcce4
Note: All data bytes are in little-endian format.
Characteristics # Name Property Max Length UUID Description SW/HW Version Read 8 f95a4b66-a721-11e9-a2a3-022ae2dbcce4 Contains the software and hardware version info OTA CMD Write 524 f95a5034-a721-11e9-a2a3-022ae2dbcce4 Command structure for OTA operations OTA Error Notify 8 ec4cff6d-81fc-4e5b-91e0-8103885c9ae3 Notifies error codes during OTA SW/HW Version # SW Version (4 bytes) HW Version (4 bytes) This characteristic reports the current software and hardware versions from the device, which helps determine whether an update is needed.</description></item><item><title>InPlayOTA App Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/tools/ota-app.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/tools/ota-app.html</guid><description>InPlayOTA App Guide # Introduction # The InPlayOTA Android App is designed for Over-the-Air (OTA) firmware upgrades for the IN6XX and IN6XXE chips. This app allows users to easily update their devices&amp;rsquo; firmware, ensuring that they are running the latest features, improvements, and bug fixes. It provides a seamless process for upgrading the firmware without the need for physical connections, enhancing the convenience and efficiency of the update procedure.</description></item></channel></rss>