<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on InPlay Doc</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/getting-started.html</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on InPlay Doc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>InPlay Inc</copyright><atom:link href="/docs/in6xxe/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BLE5.0 AT Command Set</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/getting-started/inplay-ble5.0-at-command-set.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/getting-started/inplay-ble5.0-at-command-set.html</guid><description>Inplay BLE 5.0 AT Command Set # INTRODUCTION # Inplay IN6xx BLE module is a standard Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) 5.0 certified RF module. It introduces a private service as interface of data streaming between two BLE devices transparently.
IN6xx BLE module provides the control interface based on ASCII commands, say AT commands. They are used to configure parameters, retrieve module state, control actions of module, etc. All configuration changes can be optionally remained in Non-Volatile Memory (Flash) and survive the following power cycle.</description></item><item><title>HCI Command</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/getting-started/hci_command.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/getting-started/hci_command.html</guid><description>HCI Command # Introduction to BLE HCI Commands # BLE HCI commands are standardized instructions exchanged between the host and the Bluetooth controller to manage and configure Bluetooth communication. These commands enable the host to initiate various actions, such as establishing connections, configuring parameters, and managing the overall behavior of the Bluetooth device.
HCI Command Structure # BLE HCI commands follow a specific structure, adhering to a standardized format that includes an HCI type, opcode, and parameters.</description></item><item><title>JFlash Programming</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/getting-started/jflash-download-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/getting-started/jflash-download-guide.html</guid><description>JFlash Programming Guide # Introduction # This document provides a guide on how to use J-Flash to download bin file to the IN6XXE chip.
J-Flash is a part of the J-Link tool series developed by Segger, offers a reliable solution for programming Flash memory on embedded systems.
Prerequisites # J-Link Debugger hardware.Get it on Segger web site. J-Link Software and Documentation Pack installed on your host computer(Version 7.62 or later is recommended).</description></item></channel></rss>