<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Development Guide on InPlay Doc</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/development-guide.html</link><description>Recent content in Development Guide on InPlay Doc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>InPlay Inc</copyright><atom:link href="/docs/in6xxe/development-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ADC Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/development-guide/adc-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/development-guide/adc-guide.html</guid><description>ADC Guide # Introduction # The ADC (Analog to Digital Converter) has a precision of 12 bits and operates in two modes: force mode and auto mode.
Mode # Force Mode In Force Mode, the ADC samples a single channel once and returns the result.
Auto Mode Auto Mode allows the ADC to continuously sample multiple channels. It is capable of sequential sampling across several channels. The results will be put into shared memory through DMA.</description></item><item><title>NanoSync Engine Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/development-guide/trigger-handler-guide.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/development-guide/trigger-handler-guide.html</guid><description>NanoSync Engine Guide # Introduction # NanoSync engine(trigger handler block) which can be used to perform many real-time events or tasks without the CPU’s intervention.
The NanoSync engine operates based on triggers and handlers. When a trigger (also called an event) happens, a handler will be invoked. A handler consists of a sequence of hardware actions (also called hardware tasks), which can be automatically executed by the hardware without the CPU intervention.</description></item><item><title>Run Zephyr on IN6XXE</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/development-guide/run-zephyr-on-in6xxe.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/development-guide/run-zephyr-on-in6xxe.html</guid><description>Introduction # Zephyr is an open source RTOS maintained by the Linux foundation, which is designed for connected, resource-constrained embedded devices. It provides a scalable and secure platform for developing IoT and embedded applications.
Inplay has added support including BLE for Zephyr on IN6XXE chips. If you have an IN6XXE DK board(Refer to Introduction to IN6XXE DK), you can run Zephyr BLE samples on it with this guide.
Setup a Zephyr development environment under Windows # It is recommended to develop Zephyr on IN6XXE under Windows.</description></item></channel></rss>