<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SDR Examples on InPlay Doc</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/examples-and-use-case/sdr.html</link><description>Recent content in SDR Examples on InPlay Doc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>InPlay Inc</copyright><atom:link href="/docs/in6xxe/examples-and-use-case/sdr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SDR 1 to n Sample</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/examples-and-use-case/sdr/sdr-1-master-to-multiple-slave-sample.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/examples-and-use-case/sdr/sdr-1-master-to-multiple-slave-sample.html</guid><description>SDR 1 to n Sample # Overview # SDR (Software Defined Radio) exhibits significant advantages in communication systems, especially in building flexible and multifunctional wireless communication networks. In SDR broadcast systems, signal processing and transmission are both accomplished through software. This allows SDR broadcast equipment to support multiple modulation methods, coding techniques, and transmission protocols, thus achieving compatibility with various broadcast standards. Whether it&amp;rsquo;s the high-quality audio transmission of high-definition broadcasting or the extensive coverage of digital audio broadcasting, SDR delivers excellent performance.</description></item><item><title>SDR Broadcast Sample</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/examples-and-use-case/sdr/sdr-broadcast-sample-.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/examples-and-use-case/sdr/sdr-broadcast-sample-.html</guid><description>SDR Broadcast Sample # Overview # SDR (Software Defined Radio) exhibits significant advantages in communication systems, especially in building flexible and multifunctional wireless communication networks. The Master device typically plays a central role in control and management, while multiple Slave devices serve as nodes performing specific communication tasks.
Hardware Requirements # Hardware Project Name Project Path IN628E DK proj_SDR_Broadcast_Mode_Master proj_SDR_Broadcast_Mode_Slave in-dev/proj/SDR/proj_SDR_Broadcast_Mode_Master in-dev/proj/SDR/proj_SDR_Broadcast_Mode_Slave Building # To build the sample with keil, follow the steps listed on the quick start page in the IN6xxE of Inplay Doc.</description></item></channel></rss>