<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>MultiConnNet on InPlay Doc</title><link>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet.html</link><description>Recent content in MultiConnNet on InPlay Doc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>InPlay Inc</copyright><atom:link href="/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/introduction.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/introduction.html</guid><description>Introduction to MultiConnNet System # The MultiConnNet is Inplay&amp;rsquo;s proprietary Multi-Connection Private Network system. It is a 2.4GHz wireless communication network based on a private SDR (Software Defined Radio) protocol, utilizing a one-to-many star connection topology.
The system is comprised of two primary components: the gateway module and the node module.
Key Features # Star Topology: The system employs a star connection model, with the gateway serving as the central node for bidirectional communication with multiple node modules, facilitating management and data transmission.</description></item><item><title>Module Instruction Set</title><link>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/command-set.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/command-set.html</guid><description>MultiConnNet Module Instruction Set # The MultiConnNet is Inplay&amp;rsquo;s proprietary Multi-Connection Private Network system. It is a 2.4GHz wireless communication network based on a private SDR (Software Defined Radio) protocol, utilizing a one-to-many star connection topology.
The system is comprised of two primary components: the gateway module and the node module. The module is connected to the HOST via UART, and this instruction set defines the data interaction format between the module and the HOST.</description></item><item><title>User Guild</title><link>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/user-guild.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/solutions/multiconnnet/user-guild.html</guid><description>MultiConnNet User Guild # Proper module configuration is essential before the MultiConnNet network can operate normally. However, it is necessary to understand the essential information beforehand.
Boot Mode: The module can enter Boot mode when GPIO_0_4 is connected to GND during power-up or reset, allowing for firmware flashing, storage resetting, and other operations.
Interactive Interface: By default, UART1 is used as interface between HOST and module, with GPIO_2_1 and GPIO_2_7 as TX and RX function, 921600 baud rate, 8N1.</description></item></channel></rss>