<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BLE on InPlay Doc</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/protocols-reference/ble.html</link><description>Recent content in BLE on InPlay Doc</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>InPlay Inc</copyright><atom:link href="/docs/in6xxe/protocols-reference/ble/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>BLE5.0 AT Command Set</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/protocols-reference/ble/inplay-ble5.0-at-command-set.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/protocols-reference/ble/inplay-ble5.0-at-command-set.html</guid><description>Inplay BLE 5.0 AT Command Set # INTRODUCTION # Inplay IN6xx BLE module is a standard Bluetooth Low Energy (BLE) 5.0 certified RF module. It introduces a private service as interface of data streaming between two BLE devices transparently.
IN6xx BLE module provides the control interface based on ASCII commands, say AT commands. They are used to configure parameters, retrieve module state, control actions of module, etc. All configuration changes can be optionally remained in Non-Volatile Memory (Flash) and survive the following power cycle.</description></item><item><title>GATT Programming Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/protocols-reference/ble/gatt_programming_guild.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/protocols-reference/ble/gatt_programming_guild.html</guid><description>GATT Programming Guide # Overview # The GATT (Generic Attribute) is a standard profile in BLE protocol which defines a framework of services and characteristics using ATT attributes as building blocks. The ATT protocol defineds a flat set of data structure called attributes, while GATT defines a hierarchy so that the attributes are grouped into primary and secondary services and these services can include characteristics. GATT also defines how a device will discover, read, write, notify, and indicate the characteristics based on ATT attribute access method.</description></item><item><title>Inplay Transparent Data Transmission (TRx) profile User Guide</title><link>/docs/in6xxe/protocols-reference/ble/inplay_trx_profile.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/in6xxe/protocols-reference/ble/inplay_trx_profile.html</guid><description>Inplay Transparent Data Transmission (TRx) profile User Guide # Overview # The Inplay Transparent Data Transmission (TRx) profile is a GATT based profile that fullfill tranparent data transmission function through BLE protocol. It encapsulates most of the details of the protocol stack and provides a simple interface to facilitate application development. For Inplay BLE application development, please refer to &amp;hellip; For details about GATT programming please refer to GATT Programming Guide</description></item></channel></rss>